翻译: Alicia 东仔 阿喵
嘿 Gina 要给警监签名的那份文件在你这里吗
Hey, Gina, you got that file I needed Captain Holt to sign?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
校对: Amber
后期: 凯撒
这样啊
Mm.
压制: 凯撒
Gina已经两个小时没有把视线从手机上移开了
Gina hasn't taken her eyes off her phone in two hours.
第一个让她抬头的人赢得头奖
First person to make her look up wins the pot.
我加入
I'm in.
一个能让人更有礼貌的赌约 一箭双雕
A bet which improves someone's manners? Double score.
不好意思 各位 这把我肯定赢
Sorry, guys. I got this in the bag.
以前我们滚床单的时候
I used to have to distract her from her phone
我一直都要和她手机争夺她的注意力
all the time when we were smooshin' booties.
- 恶  - 没错
- Ugh. - Yeah.
嘿 妹子
Hey, girl...
一会再聊
Catch you later.
大早上的舞蹈派对
Mid-morning dance party.
她竟然比平时跳的还好
She's dancing even better than normal.
天啊 你听说了吗 小布什死了
Oh, my God, did you hear that George W. Bush died?
那是谁
Who dat?
喔
Ooh.
Gina可能再也不会抬头看现实生活中的人了
Gina may never look at another real human being again.
她是不可战胜的
She's unbeatable.
噢 那可不一定喔
Oh, I don't know about that.
Terrence Jeffords 你开玩笑呢吧
Terrence Jeffords, are you kidding me?
我刚刚把感情状态改成了"一言难尽"
Changed my relationship status to "It's complicated."
付账吧 各位
Pony up, y'all!
唔噢
Whoo!
我老婆的电话
It's my wife.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
不不不不 我按错了
No! No, no, no. It was a mistake.
我手滑了然后就 我要回家一趟
My thumb slipped and... I have to go home.
神烦警探
第二季 第二十二集
电波诚译
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今天是我人生中最棒的一天
today is the greatest day of my life.
你们猜谁被谋杀了
Guess who just got murdered!
没错 是Carl Mather
That's right... it's Carl Mather.
什么 怎么只有我在倒吸一口凉气
What? I'm the only one gasping?
各位 这是Carl Mather啊 蹲了25年的号子
Guys, Carl Mather? Did 25 years in Attica...
不 不好意思
Sor... sorry.
需要我吸气的时候朝我指一下就好
Just point at me when you want me to gasp.
没问题
Will do.
Mather是富尔顿街四人帮成员之一
Mather is part of the Fulton Street Four.
噢
Oh!
他们从一个装甲车检修处盗窃了两千一百万美金
They stole $21 million from an armored car depot.
联邦探员抓到了他们 但一直没能把钱找回来
Feds caught them but they never found the money.
- 直到现在  - 你找回那两千一百万了吗
- Until now. - You found $21 million?
那倒没有 还没呢
Oh, God no. Not yet.
我知道我刚说的话是有点容易让人误解
I can see how that would be confusing though.
不好意思 但我会找到的
I'm sorry. But I'm going to.
过去的六个月里
Over the past six months,
这四个人都刑满释放了
all four of these guys have been released,
现在其中一人死了
and now one of them shows up dead.
肯定是有人惦记上那笔钱了
Someone's after that money,
不惜杀人来得到它
and they're willing to kill for it.
你话说的太早了吧
You're getting ahead of yourself.
你并不知道Mather的死亡
You don't know that Mather's death
一定跟那笔钱有关系
is connected to the money yet.
不要把这个案子变得比原本更复杂
Don't turn this into something bigger than it is,
尤其是在Madeline Wuntch一直看着我们的时候
not with Madeline Wuntch watching us at all times.
恶 这是什么时候挂上去的
Ew. When'd they put that in?
就在Wuntch升职之后
Right after Wuntch got promoted.
她把画像挂在高处 这样她就能
She had it installed at that height so she'd,
引用她的原话来说就是"一直俯视着我"
I quote, "Always be looking down at me," Unquote.
把这个案子当成普通案子来办
Treat this like a regular case.
警监 无意冒犯 但这是个传奇的案子
Sir, with all due respect, this is an epic case.
这就是我成为警察的原因
It's the reason I became a cop.
追查谋杀犯
I mean, hunting down a murderer,
找回被盗的百万现金
recovering millions in stolen money,
用牙叼着刀 从直升灰机上抓着绳子滑下来
rappelling out of a chopper with a knife between my teeth.
你为什么要叼着刀 从直升飞机上跳下来
Why would you jump out of a helicopter with a knife in your mouth?
是直升灰机 而我之所以会叼着刀
It's called a chopper, and the knife is in my mouth
是因为我的双手正扛着一把机关枪
because both of my hands are holding giant machine guns.
论如何正确地下飞机
And that's how it's going down.
好了 提醒一下
Okay, reminder,
明天布鲁克林公园重点(磁铁)中学要来我们这里参观
tomorrow we are hosting a field trip for the Brooklyn Park Magnet School.
不好意思 警长 我不能呆在磁铁旁边
Sorry, Sarge, I can't be around magnets.
戴着心脏起搏器呢
Pacemaker.
我还是不纠正你了
I'm actually not gonna correct you on that.
各位 这次一定不能出差错
Guys, I really need this to go well.
我女儿在这间学校的幼儿园的等候名单上
My girls are on the wait list for their preschool
而且双胞胎要进去简直难度加倍
and it's twice as tough to get in with twins.
为什么不让一个人进去读
Why don't you just get one of them in
然后让她们两个每天轮流上学
and then let them take turns going to school every other day?
Diaz 这方法太疯狂了
Diaz, that's crazy.
我问了我老婆 她说不行
I asked my wife and she said no.
这次参观一定得顺利
This field trip has to go well.
这是个能让我给校长留下深刻印象的机会
This is my chance to impress the principal.
警长 你走运了
Sarge, you're in luck.
我以前上的就是重点中学 而且我还被评为
I went to a magnet school where I was voted
"最有可能跟学校管理人员成为朋友的人"
"Most likely to befriend a school administrator."
唉 Amy
Oh, Amy.
我跟青春期前的小孩最玩的来了
Preteens are my people.
我跟他们有共同语言
I speak their language.
他们肯定会玩的很开心的
They are gonna have an amazing time.
谢谢你们 太好了
Thanks, guys. That's great.
如果你愿意 我可以给他们看一些
If you want, I can show them some of the cool stuff
证据箱里面很有意思的东西
we have in the evidence locker.
我很确定里面有一袋人手
I'm pretty sure there's a bag of hands in there.
什么 不行不行
Whoa! No. No.
我们要营造一个儿童适宜的环境
We got to make this place kid-friendly.
不要把罪案现场的照片到处放
No crime scene photos lying about.
那张不是罪案现场
That's not a crime scene.
那是我准备框起来送我老婆的闺房密照
That's a boudoir photo I'm having framed for my wife.
面具下的人就是在下
That's me underneath the mask.
老天爷
Oh, God!
接下来 我们要采访一下邻居
Next, let's get statements from the neighbors.
哦 你好啊警监
Ah, hello, Captain.
案情新发展
Quick update.
另一个富尔顿街四人帮成员今天早上被谋杀了
Another one of the Fulton Street Four was murdered here this morning.
哈 我很惊讶你没有不合时宜地庆祝这个消息
Huh, I'm surprised you're not celebrating inappropriately.
这是个罪案现场 我是个有职业操守的警察
This is a crime scene and I'm a professional.
你在我来之前庆祝了吧
You did it before I showed up?
是的 就是那样
Yeah, that is exactly correct.
两个成员在两日之内被谋杀
So two of these guys murdered in the past two days?
这肯定跟被盗的巨款有关
It has to be tied to the missing money.
承认我是对的吧
Admit I was right.
这些情况确实指示出某种联系
Circumstances do suggest a connection.
承认的直白一点
Admit it with more gusto.
- 你是对的  - 耶 你录下来了吗 Boyle
- You were right. - Yes! Did you get it, Boyle?
噢 手机相机开的是自拍模式
Oh, the camera was in selfie mode,
捕捉到了我深深为你骄傲的样子
but I look super proud of you.
坏消息是 因为这案子变大了
Unfortunately, because this case has turned out to be important,
那个女人渣(臭鼬)Madeline Wuntch把她的后腿伸向了它
that she-skunk Madeline Wuntch has her hindquarters pointed right at it.
她要我们去她办公室一趟
She wants to see us in her office,
她肯定会把这案子给重案组
no doubt to give the case to Major Crimes.
不行啊 不能让这种事发生
No, no, no. We can't let that happen.
警监 我们得做点什么
Sir, we have to do something.
好吧 我去色诱她
Fine. I'll seduce her.
我这就去穿上我的单车短裤
I'll just put on my bike shorts
让她欣赏我雄伟的下半身
and give her a glimpse of the quad cities.
不 我不是这个意思
No. No. That's not what I meant.
我的意思是我们要对抗她
I meant we have to fight her.
我们不能跟她对抗 她是魔鬼
We're not gonna fight her. She's the devil.
你不能与魔鬼共舞 因为你会被地狱之火烧伤的
And you don't dance with the devil, because you get burned.
而且 关于Madeline
Also, because in Madeline's case,
她跳舞没有节奏感 手就像老鼠的爪子一样
she has no rhythm and her hands are like little rat claws.
如果她要这个案子 那就给她
If she wants the case, it's hers.
顺便说一下 你把这个谋杀案现场
For the record, you're turning this murder scene
变成了真的无趣之地
into a real bummer-scape.
把我的有力反击拍下来了吧
Tell me you got that zinger.
噢 相机又是自拍模式
Oh, the camera was in selfie mode again,
不过我刚笑得真是灿烂啊
but I was really laughing hard.
好吧
Okay.
好了 孩子们 这就是我们警探小分队破案的地方
Okay, kids, this is where my detective squad solves crimes.
- 哇  - 这是我的办公桌
- Wow. - This is my desk.
可以通过这个我3岁女儿们自己拼的
You can tell by the framed 200-piece puzzle
200片的拼图辨认出来
my three-year-olds put together on their own.
她们很早慧嘛 Jeffords警长
That's very advanced, Sergeant Jeffords.
是吗 我也不知道什么成就能让学校招生办留下深刻印象啦
Is it? I wouldn't know what milestones are impressive to a school admissions officer.
她们能用英文和中文从1数到20
They can count to 20 in English and Mandarin.
嗨 我是Santiago警探 重点中学女校友(拉丁语)
Hi. Detective Santiago, magnet school alumna.
我很欣赏你对女校友这个词的正确用法
Well, I appreciate that you used the proper declension of alumnus.
有人说 拉丁语是一门已经死亡的语言
Well, some say Latin is a dead language,
但我觉得它只是在打一个很长的盹儿
but I say it's just taking a long nap.
瞧瞧 你们两个明显是大姐大
Okay, you two are obviously the alphas.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你在跟那个金发男孩约会 而你喜欢那个菲律宾丁日
You're dating the blond kid and you like Filipino Bieber
但你担心他还喜欢着那个编侧麻花辫 背劣质包的姑娘
but you're worried he's still into little Miss Side Braid Janky Purse.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
我什么都知道
I know so much.
嗨 我叫Gina
Hi, I'm Gina.
你好
Hey.
你好 Raymond
Hello, Raymond.
你觉得我的新办公室怎么样 在20楼哦
How do you like my new office? 20th floor.
是的 我从来没有在这么高的地方见过你
Yes, I never thought I'd see you this high
除了你骑着扫把的时候
without a broom under you.
示好结束 坐吧
Enough niceties. Have a seat.
谢谢 但我站着就好了
Thanks, but I'm actually fine standing.
我可以这样酷酷站一整天噢
I could stay in these bad boys all day.
两名富尔顿街四人帮成员被谋杀了
So two members of the Fulton Street Four
听起来是个大案子啊
have been murdered... sounds like a big case.
不是的 正好相反
No, it's actually the opposite.
就是个没啥大的情况
Pretty much an NBT sitch.
没啥大不了
No big thang.
是"没什么大不了" 但这案子是挺大不了的
The word is "Thing," And the thing is big.
我们认为有人惦记上失窃的两千一百万了
We believe someone is after the missing $21 million,
如果破了这起谋杀案 我们就能找回这笔钱
and solving this murder could lead us to the money.
是啊 但这笔钱已经差不多25岁了
Sure, but that money's, like, 25 years old.
可能都不好使了呢
It's probably not even good anymore.
对不起 抽筋了
Sorry. Cramped up.
这是个很重要的案子 Raymond
This is a very important case, Raymond,
对于我 对于纽约来说都是的
to me, and to the city of New York.
我不确定九九片区有处理这种大案的资源
I'm not sure the Nine-Nine has the resources to deal with something of this magnitude.
我懂规定
I understand the politics.
这是个备受瞩目的案子
This is a high-profile case.
做你该做的吧
Do what you must.
我想说的是
What I was going to say is,
因为你们没有那些资源
since you don't have the resources,
我会给你们提供你们需要的东西
I'll give you anything you need.
案子是你们的 我会全力支持
The case is yours. You have my full support.
什么
What?
他想表达得更激动的 像这样"神马"
He meant that more excited. Like, "What!"
好吧 富尔顿街四人帮死了两个
Okay, two of the Fulton Street Four are dead.
以我的直觉 其中一个在杀他的"同渣"
My hunch... one of them is killing off his co-scums
所以他"渣己"就能独吞赃款了
so he can keep the money for his scum-self.
我们从Reggie Bludsoe入手
We'll start with Reggie Bludsoe.
他在假释官那里留了布鲁克林的地址
He listed a Brooklyn address with his parole officer.
我们一定能搞定这人渣的
We're gonna nail this son of a bitch.
除非他无辜
Unless he's innocent...
那样我们就救下这人渣
then we're gonna have the son of a bitch.
不管怎样 这案子绝对会很棒的
Either way, this case is gonna be awesome.
Peralta 我要和你一起调查这案子
Peralta, I'm putting myself on this investigation with you.
- 什么 为什么  - Wuntch在盘算着什么
- What? Why? - Wuntch is up to something.
她让我们留着这案子只有一个原因
There's only one reason why she would let us keep this case.
她看了我一眼 然后说道
She took one look at me and said,
"我就想这小伙去开直升灰机"
"That's the guy I want flying my chopper."
你知道怎么开直升灰机吗
You know how to fly a chopper?
有什么难的
How hard could it be?
不就是个飞上天的大风扇吗
It's just a big fan that goes in the sky.
她让我们留着这案子是因为她希望我们失败
She let us keep this case because she wants us to fail.
我一起去调查
I'm coming along
这样你就不会浪费时间和资源
so that you don't waste time and resources
把这次调查弄成另一部Ron McClan的电影
turning this investigation into another Ron McClane movie.
你知道那是John McClane
Oh, you know it's John McClane.
John McClane 电影<虎胆龙威>的主角 布鲁斯·威利斯出演
我已经下定决心 就这样吧
I've made my decision. End of discussion.
那好吧
All right, fine.
但是你得自己开车
But you're gonna have to take your own car.
我把毒贩的兰博基尼从扣押处提出来了
I signed out that drug dealer's Lamborghini from the impound.
那车只有两个座位
It only has two seats.
我看到你那个申请了
I saw that you had made that request.
我换成合适的小轿车了
I changed it to a sensible sedan.
好吧 但是遮阳蓬必须打开
Okay, but the sunroof stays open.
这车没有遮阳蓬
There is no sunroof.
你当警察干什么来了
Why did you even become a cop?
干得好 孩子们
Oh, great job, kids.
别破太多案子 搞得我失业了
Don't solve too many crimes and put me out of business.
Terry还得付房租呢
Terry's got to pay the rent.
Susman老师想和我单独谈谈
Dr. Susman wants a private chat with me.
谢谢你让她感觉良好 Santiago
Thanks for warming her up, Santiago.
老师们可不会无缘无故给八年级的Amy教师休息室的钥匙
They didn't give eighth grade Amy the key to the teacher's lounge just for nothing.
我会给他们冰箱补货 在他们走后打扫清洁
I stocked their fridge and cleaned up after them.
太好了 你能接管这些孩子一会儿吗
Great. So can you take over with the kids for a minute?
他们已经完成这个活动了
They're done with this activity.
当然了 我和孩子处得可好了
Of course. I am amazing with kids.
好吧
Okay.
我和孩子完全处不来
I am terrible with kids.
我已经三年没听饶舌音乐了
I haven't listened to rap music in three years.
我不知道怎么交谈 得你来才行
I don't know the lingo. You have to do this.
不行 McKenzie在厕所里恐慌症犯了
I can't... McKenzie is in the bathroom right now freaking out
因为Kelsey S和Hayes亲热了
because Kelsey S. Made out with Hayes
尽管她知道Brianna喜欢他
even though she knows Brianna's into him.
除非你想让春季舞会成撕逼大会
So unless you want the spring dance to be a total drama fest,
否则我必须得在这儿陪她
I have to be there for her.
我没搞懂
I don't....
说实话 你应该给他们看看死人的照片
Honestly, you should show them a picture of a dead body.
不行 Rosa Terry说了要适合孩子的
No! Rosa, Terry said to keep it kid-friendly.
好吧 我就给他们看我那个年纪的时候喜欢的东西
Okay, I'll just show them the stuff that I was into when I was their age.
- 我完成了  - 我们现在干什么
- I'm done. - What do we do now?
- 接下来呢  - 你们好啊 小朋友
- What's next? - Hello, friends.
你们谁想看按照人口和时间为变量的
Who here would like to see a presentation about crime statistics
犯罪统计的报告啊
as a function of demographics and time?
谁想看死人的照片
Who wants to see a picture of a dead body?
我
Me!
Bludsoe就住在这走廊尽头
Bludsoe lives at the end of his hall.
虽然我更喜欢废弃灯塔或者破旧的仓库
Hmm... I would have preferred an abandoned lighthouse or a dilapidated barn,
但是我可以在回忆录里稍作修饰
but I can embellish in my memoirs.
噢 我等不及看那本书了
Oh, I can't wait to read that book.
你准备取什么名字
What are you gonna call it?
"快'杰'全我的一天 "
"Go Ahead, Jake My Day."
不 你的更好
No, yours is much better.
"案件完结 杰克开始"
"Case Closed, Jake Open."
- 喔  - 我懂
- Wow. - I know.
说了你的更好嘛
I said yours was better.
管他呢 我们开始吧
Whatever. Let's just do this.
纽约警局 开门
NYPD. Open up.
嘿 快看
Hey, check it out.
没打包完的行李箱
Half-packed suitcase.
看来Bludsoe准备出游
Looks like Bludsoe was planning a trip
直到被某人打扰了
until he got interrupted by someone.
- 或者某事  - 比如
- Or something. - Like what?
不知道 我只是觉得这样会增加悬念
I don't know... I just thought it would help the intrigue.
还真是
It did.
别再闲扯了
That's enough chitchat already.
别这样嘛 得有多少人被杀
Come on, how many people have to get killed
你才能开始享乐啊
before you start having fun?
你知道我们的工作是阻止人被杀吧
You do know it's our job to stop the killing, right?
等一下
Wait a second.
我好像闻到了死人的气味
I think I smell a dead body.
不对 我错了
Nope. My mistake.
等一下 别关
Wait! Don't close that.
看 指纹
Look. Handprint.
是面假墙
That's a fake wall.
纽约警局
Nypd.
把手放到头上出来
Come out with your hands on your head.
别开枪 别开枪
Don't shoot! Don't shoot.
他想杀我
He's trying to kill me.
我想噢 非要说的话
So I guess, if I had to sum them up,
Cagney的智商更高一点
Cagney is the intellectual one,
而Lacey更像是传统的那种天才
whereas Lacey is more of your traditional prodigy.
喔 你女儿们听起来都很棒啊
Well, your daughters sound great.
我会再看看她们的申请材料的
You know, I'm gonna look over their applications again.
不用劳烦了
Oh, no, that's not necessary.
姓氏是Jeffords 双写f
It's Jeffords with two Fs.
真正重要的是你的学生今天有一次美好的经历
But what really matters is that your students have an amazing experience here today.
是啊
They are.
看 Rosa 警长来了
Look, Rosa. Sarge is here.
天啊
Oh, my God.
孩子们 快离开这个房间
Children, get out of this room immediately.
快走
Let's go.
你们搞什么鬼
What the hell, guys?
他们才十二岁
They're 12 years old.
我在那个年纪愿意付出一切去看一袋人手
I would've killed to have seen a bag of hands at that age.
真是抱歉 我本想做自己 但是他们不喜欢
I'm so sorry... I tired to be myself and they hated it.
- 你去哪儿了  - 拯救这一天啊
- Where were you? - Saving the day.
Hayes已经不算事儿了
Hayes is out of the picture.
McKenzie和Kelsey S.纠纷已经解决
The McKenzie/Kelsey S. Beef is squashed,
Brianna会和Aidan一起去舞会
and Brianna's going to the dance with Aidan,
反正他也更配的上她
who's a much better match for her anyway, BT-dubs.
这对我来说有什么用
How does any of that help me?
- Susman老师  - 再见 Jeffords警长
- Dr. Susman... - Good-bye, Sergeant Jeffords.
我想这次的经历对于孩子们来说真是够了
I think this experience has been more than enough for the children.
参观就这样结束吧
We're done here.
我正从咖啡店走回家
I was walking home from the coffee shop.
我在那里谈工作
I have a job bussing tables there.
接下来 Mikey D就把一把枪抵在我背上
Anyway, the next thing I know, Mikey D has a gun in my back.
Michael D'Angelo 富尔顿四人帮的另一个成员
Michael D'Angelo, the other member of the Fulton Street Four.
嗯 不管你们信不信
Yes, believe it or not,
我很熟悉我们负责的这起备受瞩目的谋杀案中
I familiarized myself with the names of all two suspects
所有两位嫌疑人的名字
in this high-profile homicide we're investigating.
我反抗了 但是他拿了我的钥匙
I fought him off, but he got my key.
钥匙用来干什么的
What's the key for?
我们四人一人一把
Each of us had one,
你得要集齐四把才能开保险柜
and you needed all four to open the safe.
保险柜里有什么
And what's in the safe?
两千一百万美金
The $21 million.
猜 头彩
Bing... pot...
不对 我本来想说"猜中了"
Nope... I was gonna say bingo,
但是突然觉得"中头彩"更好
but then I was like, "Jackpot's better,"
但是来不及改口 已经说了一半了
but then it was too late; I was halfway through the word.
猜头彩也行 也很顺口
Bingpot works. It's taking off.
是很顺口
It's taking off.
警监 D'Angelo在州北部有房产
Captain, D'Angelo has a place upstate.
当地治安官说现在就有辆车停在车道上
The local sheriff says there's a car in the driveway right now.
他一定在那儿
He must be there.
好吧 他们得自己突击了 不能等我们
Okay, they're gonna have to raid the place without us.
我们到达得花两个小时
It'll take us two hours to get up there.
或者我们可以坐
Or we could take...
我们不会坐直升飞机
We are not taking a helicopter.
你知道我是想说直升灰机
You know I was gonna say chopper.
Peralta 我知道你在享乐
Look, Peralta, I know you're having fun,
但如果一旦出了差错 出动直升飞机这种浪费经费的行为
but a helicopter is exactly the kind of wasteful expenditure
就会被Wuntch用来打击我
that Wuntch will use to bury me if something goes wrong.
- 好吧 长官  - 或许
- Okay, sir... - Or...
如果我没用的话 她也会拿来攻击我
It's the kind of thing she'll crucify me for not getting.
"你本可以使用直升灰机的 Raymond"
"You could've had a chopper, Raymond.
"为什么不充分利用资源呢"
"Why didn't you take advantage?
等一等 我现在脑子有点乱
Just a minute... my cauldron's boiling over."
但实际上她说的是
Yeah, but what she actually said was,
"直升机是你的了 Peralta"
"Chopper's yours, Peralta."
你学得更像
Your impression was better.
你做了什么
What did you do?
她也许打电话给我了 我也许和她汇报了情况
She may have called me and I may have briefed her
而她也许同意了使用直升灰机
and she may have said yes to the chopper
因为直升灰机正在途中
because it's definitely on its way right now!
中间位置是我的
I call middle seat!
喔
Whoo!
这太棒了
This is awesome!
好吧 我们说清楚 从现在开始
Okay, just so we're clear, from this point forward,
我的代号是死亡剑客
my call sign will be Death Blade.
我的是Rum Tum Tugger
And I'll be Rum Tum Tugger.
不行 Boyle 不能用音乐剧<猫>里的角色名
No, Boyle. No characters from Cats.
好好想想 想个吓人的名字
Dig deep. Think of something scary.
阿道夫·希特勒
Adolf Hitler.
不行
No!
你就叫 响尾蛇
You will be... Sidewinder.
好吧 但是希特勒更吓人
All right, but I'm more scared of Hitler.
你呢 警监 你的代号是什么
How about you, Captain? What's your call sign?
我就叫Raymond Holt警监
I will be Captain Raymond Holt.
我就知道你不会配合
Uh-huh, I knew you wouldn't play ball.
所以你的代号是扫兴鬼
And that is why your call sign is Wet Blanket.
响尾蛇 我是死亡剑客
Sidewinder, this is Death Blade.
收到了吗 响尾蛇 完毕
Do you copy, Sidewinder? Over.
我是响尾蛇 死亡剑客
This is Sidewinder, Death Blade.
你的消息已收到 完毕
I read you loud and clear. Over.
你有发现扫兴鬼的位置吗 响尾蛇
Do you have a 20 on Wet Blanket, Sidewinder?
完毕
Over.
- 我发现了  - 完毕
- I do have a visual... - Over.
好了 警监
All right, look, Captain,
Wuntch说了 为了解决这案子
Wuntch said that we could have anything we needed
我们要什么都行
to solve this case.
是啊 但是为什么呢
Yes, but why?
为了抓住一个偷了两千一百万的杀人犯
To catch a murder who stole $21 million.
不 是为了让我们的失败显得更加引人注目
No, it's so that when we do fail, it'll be that much more spectacular.
如果我们不抓到D'Angelo 我的事业就完了
If we don't get D'Angelo, my career is over.
但是如果我们抓到了他 你的事业就会真正地腾飞
But if we do catch him, your career will really take off.
直升灰机双关语
Chopper pun!
Susman博士 我真的非常非常抱歉
Dr. Susman, I am so, so sorry.
拜托不要因为这个针对我的女儿们
Please don't hold this against my daughters.
我绝不会那样做
I would never do that.
预科学校招生是基于我们对家长的看法
Preschool admissions are based on what we think of the parents.
噢 不
Oh, no.
Susman博士
Dr. Susman...
Nancy 如果我可以这样称呼你的话
Nancy, if I may...
- 你不可以  - 好的
- You may not. - Okay.
听着 我们的方法可能有点非传统
Look, our methods may have been a little unorthodox,
也许还有一点
and perhaps a little...
过度形象并且令人作呕
Graphic and disgusting.
我本来想说小恶心的
I was gonna go with yucky...
但是这些孩子今天玩得很开心
But these kids had fun today.
并且学到了很多
And they learned a lot.
Tricia 什么是鲁米诺
Tricia, what's Luminol?
它用于在犯罪现场寻找血迹
It's used to look for blood in a crime scene.
即使罪犯试图清理血迹
Even if a criminal tried to clean it up,
血液中的铁使得化学物质发光
the iron in blood makes the chemical glow.
还有 Bobby 什么叫眼球摘除术
And, Bobby, what's enucleation?
就是有人把你的眼珠子弹出来
It's when someone pops your eyeball out.
当时应该举个不那么恶心的例子
Probably should've used a less gross example.
重点是
The point is,
正是这样的教育经历让我热爱我的重点学校
this is exactly the kind of educational experience i loved about my magnet school.
这一点还有待讨论
Well, there's something to be said for that.
还有 更重要的是
Also, and more importantly,
我让McKenzie和Brianna不再讨厌Kelsey S了
I got McKenzie and Brianna to stop hating on Kelsey S.
现在他们是最好的朋友了 不用谢
And now they're best friends... you're welcome.
哇哦 那其实挺厉害的
Wow, that's actually impressive.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以 Susman博士
So, Dr. Susman,
让我们为这次参观之旅正名
let's just call this field trip what it was...
这是一次巨大的成功
a huge success.
它挺 有趣的
It was... interesting.
我看到了一个妓女耶
I saw a prostitute.
别帮倒忙了 小子
Not helping, kid.
D'Angelo的住处就在那些树后面
D'Angelo's place is just beyond those trees.
还没有人进出
No one's gone in or out.
幸好我们及时赶到
Good thing we got here in time.
坐直升灰机过来的
Flew in on a chopper.
Bell412还是A119Koala
Bell 412 or the A119 Koala?
这是机密
It's classified.
事实上 是一架350B2
Actually, it was the 350B2.
不错
Nice.
不 别让他说"不错"
No, don't give him the "Nice."
我们还没有看到任何屋内的动静
We haven't seen any movement in the house,
但是谷仓里有灯光
but there are lights on in the barn.
这有个谷仓
There's a barn?
你为什么对谷仓这么痴迷
What is your fascination with barns?
那是所有屌炸天的对决发生的地方
It's where all the awesome stand-offs happen...
生锈的农场用具 光线从弹孔透入
rusty farm equipment, light shining through bullet holes.
我跟你打赌至少会有一只鸽子慢动作起飞
I'll bet you at least one dove takes flight in slo-mo.
我跟你赌 因为那是不可能的
I will take that bet, because that's impossible.
后门有一支小分队
We've got a team on the back entrance,
一队人在盯着房子 那座小山上还有个狙击手
a team watching the house, and a marksman on that hill.
好 告诉你的人如果他们先找到钱
Okay, tell your men if they find the money first,
让我在耳边洗一遍然后说
that I get to riffle it next to my ear and go,
"都在这儿了"
"It's all here."
- 已经告诉他们了 Jake  - 爱你 兄弟
- Already told them, Jake. - Love you, bud.
好了 子弹上膛伙计们
All right, let's lock and load.
飞得比我想象的快 但还是很酷
Moved faster than I was expecting, but still cool.
我看不到他
I don't see him.
噢 他在这儿呢
Oh, he's here.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
他在呢 他死了
He is. He's dead.
- 什么  - 尸体就在这里
- What? - The body is right here.
该死 Bludsoe耍了我们
Damn it! Bludsoe played us.
快接 快接 快接
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
- 哈喽  - 嘿 我是Peralta
- Hello? - Hey, it's Peralta.
Bludsoe还在拘留中吗
Is Bludsoe still in custody?
是啊 我们关着他呢 他在他的
Yeah, we got him. He's in his...
哎哟
Ooh.
所以 先说好消息
So... good news first.
我们回去会飞过美丽的日落
We're gonna be flying back past a beautiful sunset.
坏消息 Bludsoe从医院逃跑了
Bad news... Bludsoe escaped from the hospital
我们都完蛋了
and we're all screwed.
但是 有漂亮的日落噢
But... Pretty sunset.
哦 伙计 看看警监
Oh, man, look at the captain.
他在缓慢地踱步
He's pacing slowly.
对于他 那就像全开的愤怒大爆发
For him, that's like a full-on, rage-fueled freak out.
唯一更糟的就是他站着一动不动的时候
The only thing worse is when he stands perfectly still.
哦 不 他完全静止了
Oh, no, he's standing perfectly still.
好了 我要去跟他谈谈
All right, I'm gonna go talk to him.
嗯 不我不去
Mm, no I'm not.
是的 我要去 不 我才不去
Yep, I am. No, I'm not gonna do it.
好了 我去 我这就去
Okay, I am. I'm gonna go.
好 小心点
Okay. Be careful.
- 你真勇敢  - 谢谢
- You're so brave. - Thanks.
嘿 警监
Hey, Captain.
你在想什么呢
What you thinking about?
主要是Madeline Wuntch会怎么毁灭我
Mostly about how Madeline Wuntch will destroy me
就因为你想要一架直升机来演动作片
because you wanted a helicopter to play action movie.
我需要直升机是因为我在追捕一个坏人
I needed the helicopter because I was chasing a bad guy
因为我是个警察
because I'm a cop.
真的吗 不是只想要让这个案子变得传奇吗
Really? It wasn't just to make this case epic?
这个案子是很传奇
This case is epic.
你只是被政治蒙混了头脑看不见
You're just too wrapped up in the politics to see it.
长官 我们在追踪一个偷了两千一百万美金
Sir, we're tracking a triple murderer
杀了三个人的罪犯
who stole $21 million,
你能想到的只有Madeline Wuntch
and all you can think about is Madeline Wuntch.
- 你说得对  - 你说什么
- You're right. - What's that now?
在我来九九片区之前
Before I came to the Nine-Nine,
我被困在公共关系部门的一个办公桌后面慢慢腐烂
I was rotting away behind a desk in the public relations department.
我想要的只是一个再次做个好警察的机会
All I wanted was the chance to do good police work again.
我刚得到这个机会 我却浪费它想着那个邪恶的癞蛤蟆
I just got it, and I blew it thinking about that devil toad.
我受够政治了
I'm tired of politics.
我们去抓住那个混蛋Bludsoe
Let's get that punk! Bludsoe.
这真是棒呆了
This is amazing.
当然 我们完全不知道他在哪里
Of course, we have no idea where he is,
但是我欣赏你的想法
but I love where your head's at.
他没有家人
He has no family.
也许有个女朋友
Maybe there was a girlfriend
或者某个咖啡店的同事
or someone he worked with at the coffee shop.
咖啡店 为什么一个知道自己会有两千一百万美元的人
The coffee shop... why would someone who knows they have $21 million coming
会做一份最低薪资的工作呢
take a minimum wage job?
因为他需要进入那栋建筑
Because he needed access to that building.
因为那就是钱藏着的地方
Because that's where the money's hidden.
好了 我们得尽快赶到那儿
All right, we got to get there quick.
也许我们应该坐直升灰机
Maybe we should take the chopper.
你说了直升灰机
You said chopper.
死亡刀锋 响尾蛇 是时候出发了
Death Blade, Sidewinder, it's go time!
收到 扫兴鬼
Roger that, Wet Blanket.
不 从今以后 叫我
No, from now on, call me...
天鹅绒雷霆
Velvet Thunder.
好的
Okay.
嘿 Cagney和Lacey离开等候名单了
Hey, Cagney and Lacey got off the wait list.
谢谢你们帮我
Thank you, guys, for helping me.
Rosa 我本应该听你的
Rosa, I should've listened to you.
是啊 每个人都应该听我的
Yeah, everyone should listen to me
不论何时 不论何事
all the time about everything.
还挺好玩的 孩子们其实喜欢我
It was pretty fun. The kids actually liked me.
我希望我能回到初中
I wish I could go back to middle school
带着我现在的知识
knowing what I know now.
我一定超酷的
I'd be so cool.
我还能重做所有的考试
And I'd get to retake all the tests.
更新一些读书报告
And update some book reports.
噢 对了 Gina Susman博士说
Oh, un, Gina, Dr. Susman said
你对那些孩子产生了真正的影响
you had a real impact on those kids.
显然 你刚被命名为春季舞会公主
Apparently, you were just named spring Dance Princess somehow.
嗯哼 我一直以来都跟你们说什么呢
Mm-hmm, what am I always telling you guys?
我是皇族
I'm royalty.
好了 听着
All right, listen up.
我们快速有力地出击
We go in strong and we go in fast.
Evans 你负责破门
Evans, you're on door breach.
Patterson 你扔闪光弹
Patterson... flashbang.
Boyle 别再那么深蹲了
Boyle, stop squatting like that.
抱歉 我以为这样很酷
Sorry, I thought it looked cool.
- 并没有  - 数三下
- It didn't. - On the count of three.
是Bludsoe
It's Bludsoe!
- 纽约警局  - 走 走 走
- NYPD! - Go, go, go!
脸朝下 趴在地上
Facedown, flat on the ground!
嘿 这里 这里
Hey, over here, over here.
猜头彩
Bingpot!
太酷了
This rules.
你知道我的梦想一直是
Did you know that my dream has always been to
和一堆被追回的现金合照吗
have my picture taken with a mountain of recovered cash?
我一直以来的梦想就是给你照那张照片 Jake
And it's always been my dream to take that picture of you, Jake.
- 噢  - 耶
- Oh. - Yeah.
耶
Yeah!
两千一百万 Raymond
$21 million, Raymond.
我必须承认 你让我刮目相看
I have to admit, I'm impressed.
抱歉让你失望了 Madeline
Sorry to disappoint you, Madeline.
我知道你希望我们失败
I know you'd hoped we'd fail.
哦不 我高兴得不得了
Oh, no, I couldn't be happier.
等等 你为什么那么说
Wait... Why would you say that?
你为什么没有愤怒地握紧你的小老鼠爪子
And why aren't you clenching your little rat hands in anger?
你不想让我失败
You didn't want me to fail.
你想让我成功
You wanted me to succeed.
没错
That's right.
我正在找借口把你升到一个文职上去
I was looking for an excuse to promote you to a desk job,
你就把这个借口放在银盘子上
and you handed it to me on a silver platter
用你的小老鼠爪子奉上了
with your little rat hands.
噢 不
Oh, no.
对九九片区说再见吧 Raymond
Say good-bye to the Nine-Nine, Raymond.
我要任命你为纽约警局的公共关系部长
I'm making you head of NYPD Public Relations.
警监 过来和我一起
Captain, get in here with me.
去吧 对镜头微笑 Raymond
Go ahead. Smile for the cameras, Raymond.
这是你的新工作了
That's your new job now.
嘿
Hey!
好了 快点 我们来背对背摆造型
Okay, quick, let's pose back-to-back
双手交叉再来个神气的斜笑
with our arms crossed and a cocky smirk.
你在做吗 双手交叉了没
You doing it? Your arms crossed?
没有 手放下 那也不错
No, arms down. That's good.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组